<net.rptools.maptool.model.MacroButtonProperties>
  <macroUUID>5e08e90d-dbe5-4597-a033-7492c7cef115</macroUUID>
  <saveLocation>Token</saveLocation>
  <index>162</index>
  <colorKey>default</colorKey>
  <hotKey>None</hotKey>
  <label>dnd5e_SavedAttacks_applyRolledExpression</label>
  <group>Saved Attacks</group>
  <sortby/>
  <autoExecute>true</autoExecute>
  <includeLabel>false</includeLabel>
  <applyToTokens>false</applyToTokens>
  <fontColorKey>black</fontColorKey>
  <fontSize>1.00em</fontSize>
  <minWidth/>
  <maxWidth/>
  <allowPlayerEdits>true</allowPlayerEdits>
  <toolTip>&lt;html&gt;Determine what a single rolled RollExpression step should do by type. 
&lt;br&gt;Each step is executed against the target token.
&lt;dl&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;&lt;b&gt;Attack&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dd&gt;Determine if the attack roll is larger than the AC of the target. 
&lt;br&gt;Steps after this check are skipped if the attack missed until the next attack. 
&lt;br&gt;This step is ignored if a previous Target Check has failed.&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;&lt;b&gt;Damage&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dd&gt;Apply damage to the target. This step is ignored if a previous Attack missed or
&lt;br&gt;a previous Target Check has failed.&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;&lt;b&gt;Save Damage&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dd&gt;Apply damage to the target. An earlier Save is checked to see if the damage should
&lt;br&gt;be modified by the save effect. The value &apos;none&apos;, &apos;half&apos; and a multiplier are supported.
&lt;br&gt;This step is ignored if a previous Attack missed or a previous Target Check has failed.
&lt;br&gt;If created by the attack editor the save is included with this step. A save roll is
&lt;br&gt;created and rolled against the target before determining the damage applied. See the Save step.&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;&lt;b&gt;Save&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dd&gt;Roll a save against the target. The roll result is compared to the save DC to determine if the save
&lt;br&gt;passed or failed. This result can then be used by later Save Damage and Save Condition steps.
&lt;br&gt;This step is ignored if a previous Attack missed or a previous Target Check has failed.&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;&lt;b&gt;Condition&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dd&gt;Apply these conditions to the target. This step is ignored if a prvious Attack missed or a previous 
&lt;br&gt;Target Check has failed.&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;&lt;b&gt;Save Condition&lt;/b&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dd&gt;Apply these conditions to the target after checking the result of a previous Save step. Conditions can
&lt;br&gt;be applied either when the save pass or when it fails, but not both. This step is ignored if a previous 
&lt;br&gt;Attack missed or a previous Target Check has failed.&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;&lt;b&gt;Target Check&lt;/b&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dd&gt;Execute a check agasint the target token. The result is either pass or fail. On a fail steps after this
are skipped until the next target check. This step is ignored if a previous Attack missed.&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;/dl&gt;
&lt;br&gt;arg(0) = id of target token 
&lt;br&gt;arg(1) = The single roll expression step being applied
&lt;br&gt;arg(2) = The current state for all rolled RollExpressions previously applied
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Returns the updated state object.
&lt;br&gt;See &lt;font face=&quot;monospace&quot;&gt;dnd5e_SavedAttacks_updateState&lt;/font&gt; for format
&lt;html&gt;</toolTip>
  <displayHotKey>true</displayHotKey>
  <commonMacro>false</commonMacro>
  <compareGroup>true</compareGroup>
  <compareSortPrefix>true</compareSortPrefix>
  <compareCommand>true</compareCommand>
  <compareIncludeLabel>true</compareIncludeLabel>
  <compareAutoExecute>true</compareAutoExecute>
  <compareApplyToSelectedTokens>true</compareApplyToSelectedTokens>
</net.rptools.maptool.model.MacroButtonProperties>
